{
    "subject": "Frances_Langford",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jon_Hall",
    "human_readable": "Frances Langford is married to Jon Hall.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9873948097229004,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Frances Langford and Jon Hall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9844669103622437,
            "question": "Are Frances Langford and Jon Hall spouses?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9272375702857971,
            "question": "To whom is Frances Langford married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9191880822181702,
            "question": "Who is Frances Langford married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8709738850593567,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Frances Langford and Jon Hall?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8387197256088257,
            "question": "Name the husband of Frances Langford."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6982389688491821,
            "question": "Is Frances Langford in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6567369699478149,
            "question": "What is the name of Jon Hall's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6544715762138367,
            "question": "What is the name of Jon Hall's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5906904935836792,
            "question": "Who is Jon Hall?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frances Langford is married to Jon Hall.",
            "html": "yago_7912_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jon Hall's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_7912_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jon Hall's wife?",
            "html": "yago_7912_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Frances Langford in a relationship?",
            "html": "yago_7912_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7912_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7912_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7912_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7912_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7912_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7912_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7912_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7912_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7912_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7912_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7912/re-ranker-msmarco/93.txt, it is mentioned that \"Jon Hall and Frances Langford were married for 20 years.\"\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7912/re-ranker-msmarco/64.txt, it is stated that \"Langford was married to Jon Hall.\"\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7912/re-ranker-msmarco/79.txt, there is a photo of Frances Langford with her first husband, Jon Hall.\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7912/re-ranker-msmarco/19.txt, it is mentioned that \"The couple purchased 400 acres of land in Jensen Beach just before WWII, and the couple split amicably in 1955\", which implies that Jon Hall was indeed Frances Langford's husband.\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_7912/re-ranker-msmarco/89.txt, it is stated that \"Hall was married three times, two of which were to entertainers: singer Frances Langford and actress Raquel Torres.\"\n\nTherefore, the triple \"Frances Langford is married to Jon Hall\" is supported by the provided context information.\n\nThe final answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Jon Hall and Frances Langford were married, supporting the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}